[
  { "question": "Leben", "answer": "βιο", "phonetic": "vío" },
  { "question": "Wort / Lehre", "answer": "λόγος", "phonetic": "ló-gos" },
  { "question": "Gott", "answer": "θεός", "phonetic": "the-ós" },
  { "question": "Liebe", "answer": "φίλος", "phonetic": "fí-los" },
  { "question": "Stern", "answer": "ἄστρον", "phonetic": "ÁS-tron" },
  { "question": "Erde", "answer": "γῆ / γεω-", "phonetic": "yee / yéo" },
  { "question": "Schreiben", "answer": "γράφω", "phonetic": "GRÁ-fo" },
  { "question": "Zeit", "answer": "χρόνος", "phonetic": "CHRÓ-nos" },
  { "question": "Mensch", "answer": "ἄνθρωπος", "phonetic": "ÁN-thro-pos" },
  { "question": "Furcht", "answer": "φόβος", "phonetic": "FÓ-vos" },
  { "question": "Kraft", "answer": "δύναμις", "phonetic": "DÝ-na-mis" },
  { "question": "Wasser", "answer": "ὕδωρ", "phonetic": "Ý-thor" },
  { "question": "Feuer", "answer": "πῦρ", "phonetic": "pýr" },
  { "question": "Seele", "answer": "ψυχή", "phonetic": "psichí" },
  { "question": "Licht", "answer": "φῶς", "phonetic": "fos" },
  { "question": "Wissenschaft / Kenntnis", "answer": "γνῶσις", "phonetic": "GNÓ-sis" },
  { "question": "Kind", "answer": "παῖς", "phonetic": "pés / pési" },
  { "question": "Tier", "answer": "ζῷον", "phonetic": "ZÓ-on" },
  { "question": "Ordnung / Welt", "answer": "κόσμος", "phonetic": "KÓS-mos" },
  { "question": "Form / Gestalt", "answer": "μορφή", "phonetic": "mor-FÍ" },
  { "question": "Sprache / Rede", "answer": "ῥῆμα", "phonetic": "RÍ-ma" },
  { "question": "Schule", "answer": "σχολή", "phonetic": "scho-LÍ" },
  { "question": "Stimme / Ton", "answer": "φωνή", "phonetic": "fo-NÍ" },
  { "question": "Tod", "answer": "θάνατος", "phonetic": "THÁ-na-tos" },
  { "question": "Luft / Atem", "answer": "πνεῦμα", "phonetic": "PNÉV-ma" },
  { "question": "Bewegung", "answer": "κίνησις", "phonetic": "KÍ-ni-sis" },
  { "question": "Sehen", "answer": "ὁράω", "phonetic": "o-RÁ-o" },
  { "question": "Lichtbild / Bild", "answer": "εἰκών", "phonetic": "i-KÓN" },
  { "question": "Wärme", "answer": "θέρμη", "phonetic": "THÉR-mi" },
  { "question": "Gericht / Urteil", "answer": "κρίσις", "phonetic": "KRÍ-sis" },
  { "question": "Energie / Wirksamkeit", "answer": "ἐνέργεια", "phonetic": "e-NÉR-yeia" },
  { "question": "Feind", "answer": "ἐχθρός", "phonetic": "ech-THRÓS" },
  { "question": "Körper", "answer": "σῶμα", "phonetic": "SÓ-ma" },
  { "question": "Herz", "answer": "καρδία", "phonetic": "kar-DÍA" },
  { "question": "Gehirn / Verstand", "answer": "ἐγκέφαλος", "phonetic": "en-GÉ-fa-los" },
  { "question": "Lärm / Klang", "answer": "θόρυβος", "phonetic": "THÓ-ry-vos" },
  { "question": "Buch", "answer": "βιβλίον", "phonetic": "vi-VLÍ-on" },
  { "question": "Stadt", "answer": "πόλις", "phonetic": "PÓ-lis" },
  { "question": "Mitte / Zentrum", "answer": "κέντρον", "phonetic": "KÉN-tron" },
  { "question": "Farbe", "answer": "χρῶμα", "phonetic": "CHRÓ-ma" }
]
